Why are we going through all this
again? I had my trial. I went to jail.
And never finished your sentence.
You have two options.
You go back to prison
or you do a little work
for the Department of Damage...
Two. Option two. thanks.
Do you think you can
get close to him?
Hey. isn't that
for American Horror Story?
Sorry. Day players
don't get golf carts.
The showrunner just called.
He's cutting your character from the show.
I want you to wear this.
Find his computer
and place this right on top.
and I'll handle the rest remotely.
I shouldn't have left them alone.
I knew I shouldn't have left them alone.
It's just so hard
since their father passed.
I can't be everywhere at once.
Take a deep breath for me.
and blow out hard and fast.
You're sure he was inside
when the fire broke out?
He was in the room where it started.
The firefighter had to break
into the kitchen to get him.
I called 911 as soon as I smelled smoke.
What is it?
It's okay. Just wait.
Mrs. Williams. your son
shows no signs of smoke inhalation.
He's got no cough. no burns.
Not even skin irritation.
I don't think I've seen
a healthier 13-year-old in my life.
- So. it's all okay?
- It's great.
We could do a chest x-ray.
but I really don't think that's necessary.
Oh. thank goodness!
But you should be more
careful when using the stove on your own.
It was the stove. right?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you!
Supernatural threats.
That's our simple directive.
Protect this country
from supernatural threats.
We've got the men. and women.
The resources.
And an incredibly expensive.
state-of-the-art. high-security prison.
We have everything we need
to do an essential job for our nation.
There's just one problem.
Do you know what the problem is?
Our prison is half-empty.
Half-empty!
And the Congressional Budget Office
is up our ass.
looking at every nickel and dime
we're costing the taxpayer.
We're facing significant budget cuts
at every office.
20% or more.
here in Los Angeles.
Every single person here
is gonna need to look carefully
at what you're contributing.
♪ Now what up. everybody?
Let me set the scene ♪
♪ Fresh new start for your boy. Young Z! ♪
♪ You saw Pops. for a dad. he's cool ♪
♪ He's just a little stressed
About my first day of school ♪
♪ They say.
"Be careful. 'cause humans can be mean" ♪
♪ But I'm still going out
For the football team ♪
♪ It might be rough
But it's home sweet home ♪
♪ Just a little bit of dust
And a little bit of mold ♪
♪ But it ain't so bad
On this side of the track... ♪
There are so many self-tapes.
I'd say.
Here's what we know.
We have the police reports
of the kitchen fire when Simon was 13.
We have last year's port-o-potty explosion
on the set of The Rookie.
And thanks to you and Simon's hard drive.
we can place him at the scene.
- It's almost enough.
- And you're sure he's dangerous?
For what it's worth.
he seems like a sensitive soul to me.
- I'll put that in the file. Trevor.
- Just saying.
- Simon's mother's birthday is tomorrow.
- Oh.
He's going to her party in Pacoima.
I want you there.
and I want you wearing a wire.
Do some digging
with the family about the fire.
Get me something I can use.
This feels like
we might be crossing a line.
Well. if you don't.
you're going back to prison.
- Wait. that wasn't the deal.
- Well. it is now.
You're going soft.
and I don't have any time to waste.
Get me something I can use. or we're done.
Lovely to meet you. Mrs. Williams.
Well. if Von Kovak
is still watchin' tapes.
then maybe a little phone call
to remind him...
Mmm-mmm.
No. Simon. it's crazy here.
Do you know who we're about to sign?
The Manning brothers.
And they come as a package deal.
We're playin' hot potato with Eli.
and I don't wanna be left holdin'
- that dead weight.
- Well. good luck. I'll just sit here
not thinking about how life-changing
it'll be to hear back from Von Kovak.
If there is news. you know
you'll be the first to know.
unless you call me again.
in which case. I will never tell you.
- That's not funny.
- Good. 'cause I wasn't tryin' to be funny.
You know. if they don't give you
a callback. it means they're clowns
making a terrible movie
you wouldn't want to be a part of anyway.
Yeah.
Besides. the work of an actor
isn't getting jobs.
Your work is acting.
You can always find a way to act.
Yeah. you're right.
I have to stop waiting for permission.
If I don't get this part. I should
do somethin' on my own.
A short film. a play...
A play. Yes. "The play's the thing."
Theater. purest form of acting.
"Rumble thy bellyful!
"Spit. fire.
"Spout. rain.
"Nor rain. wind. thunder.
fire are my daughters!
"I tax not you.
you elements. with unkindness.
"I never gave you kingdom.
call'd you children!
"You owe me no subscription!
"Then let fall your horrible pleasure!"
Not bad.
You know this one?
"Well. maybe it's like Casey says.
"'Maybe a fella ain't got a soul
of his own. Just...
"'a little piece of a big soul.
"'One big soul that belongs to everybody.
"'Then...
"'Then it don't matter.
"'I'll be all around. in the dark.
"'I'll be everywhere.
"'Wherever you can look.
"'Wherever there's a fight
so hungry people can eat. I'll be there.
"'Wherever there's a cop beatin' up
on a guy. I'll be there...'"
"On the page. it looked like nothing.
"The beginning. simple. almost comical.
"Just a pulse.
"Bassoons and basset horns.
like a rusty squeeze box.
"But then. high above it. an oboe.
"Just a single note
hanging there. unwavering.
"until a clarinet
took over and sweetened it...
"to a phrase of such delight.
"This was no composition
by a performing monkey.
"This was a music I'd never heard before.
"Filled with such longing.
"such unfulfillable longing.
"it had me trembling.
"It seemed to me
that I was hearing the voice of God."
- Sorry.
- Oh. please.
Well done. by the way.
Thanks.
Oh. I gotta go.
I'm supposed to be in Pacoima
for my mom's birthday later.
A birthday celebration in Pacoima?
How exciting!
You think that sounds exciting?
Well. I've never been to Pacoima before.
I grew up there. and I promise
you haven't missed anything.
It's basically Cleveland with palm trees.
Well. I've never been to Cleveland either.
Do you mind if I tag along?
Uh...
Would be nice to have a buffer.
It's gonna be just a bunch of aunties
and cousins sharing war stories
of growing up Haitian.
I've always been an exceptional buffer.
Good.
Uh. look. my family doesn't know
I got fired from American Horror Story.
- Oh.
- So... let's keep that between us.
As Belinda Carlisle famously sang.
"Our lips are sealed."
♪ Can you hear them? ♪
♪ They talk about us ♪
♪ Telling lies
Well. that's no surprise ♪
♪ Can you see them?
See right through them ♪
♪ They have no shield
No secrets to reveal ♪
♪ Doesn't matter what they say ♪
♪ In the jealous games people play ♪
♪ Our lips are sealed ♪
Hey.
Hey. Happy birthday. Mummi.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh. you're right on time.
Mummi. this is Trevor. my industry friend.
It's lovely to meet you. Mrs. Williams.
Oh. it's so nice
to meet one of Simon's work friends.
Ooh! And I love your fashion style.
I hope you don't mind me
intruding on your party.
Ah. no problem.
Friends are always welcome here.
My son. Eric. just had
my kitchen renovated for my birthday.
Oh!
You'll never believe the transformation.
He never saw it before. Mummi.
You'll be able to tell.
I've been telling everyone
about your American Horror Story movie.
It's not a movie. Mummi. it's television.
But it's a big show!
Everyone at church is so excited
you're gonna be on YouTube!
Anything streaming is on "YouTube."
So. this is where Simon grew up?
Simon was born right in this house.
I wasn't born in the house.
Well. he knows what I mean.
Eric! Your brother is here!
Hey.
Was traffic bad?
It was normal.
Did you bring the whipped cream?
Oh!
- I can go out.
- I asked you to do one thing. man.
Who needs whipped cream
when we are having cake?
- Thank you.
- Absolutely. Cake should stand alone.
Why do you look familiar?
Trevor Slattery. Trained
at the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art.
Did bits and bobs in the West End.
Weren't you The Mandarin?
Then I took a role.
posing as an international terrorist
to pay my drug and prostitution debts.
You have to see the new kitchen.
Give them the tour.
Follow me.
And he put in an island.
I always wanted an island.
And check this out.
- A refrigerator just for wine.
- Oh. my.
Oh!
Trevor. are you a wine guy?
Oh. no. thank you.
A bit of a teetotaler these days.
13 years sober.
Oh. good for you.
Well. um. congratulations
on a lovely kitchen.
What did it look like before?
Beige and dark orange. Really '70s.
The cabinets were all
that dark wood paneling.
Remember that?
- No. not really.
- It was before the fire.
Oh. there was a fire?
Yeah. it was a long time ago.
Oh. what happened?
Why do you want to know?
Oh. just making conversation.
It's not much of a story.
It certainly sounds like one.
A kitchen. a fire.
it's packed with drama already.
- Eric still blames me.
- We don't need to talk about it.
I mean. what 13-year-old doesn't
understand how a stove works?
It was my fault
for leaving Simon alone in the house.
Oh. so Simon was alone when it happened?
Hey. how you been?
Oh. okay...
All right. Hold on. Bam!
That's Walter. That's Fritz. That's Alex.
Martha and I practically
raised our kids together.
They would spend hours in that backyard.
What was Simon like as a child?
Quiet.
Interesting.
That's all you've got to say?
I have never much liked him. to be honest.
his brother. Eric. he's the nice one.
So helpful!
I wasn't asking
for your preference. Esther.
Just some Simon stories. Bloody hell.
- Oh?
- Oh.
Word. So you ever meet
any famous people or any superheroes?
Uh. nah. not really.
- Damn.
- I love Captain America.
He is the full package.
But he is just like a regular dude
who can throw a shield. right?
Oh. Is that how you feel?
Simon and I used to carpool together
to school every day.
Oh. you must have so many stories.
Oh. was he. you know. shaken up
after the kitchen fire?
We didn't talk much.
But you carpooled every day?
Yeah.
- So. like. what are your hours?
- Yeah.
It's actually kinda unpredictable.
'Cause. just. like.
just last week I had. what.
three auditions...
- Three auditions.
- And an acting class.
Is that a lot for a week?
That's a full week.
- Wow!
- Oh. that's a full week.
Chunky. you stupid.
You know
I can understand you. right?
- Oh! Yeah. I'm glad your Creole is good.
- I was just...
Top five memories of Simon's childhood.
Whatever comes to mind.
Excuse me. Hey. man. what are you doing?
I thought you were gonna be my buffer.
I just spent 20 minutes explaining
producer sessions to my cousins.
Sorry. I'm just so excited
to meet everyone.
- Now I know you're lying.
- What? I'm not lying.
No one's happy to talk
to my neighbor. Esther.
Yeah. No. Sh... She's terrible.
All right. folks.
Let's eat!
- Oh. man. Full plate!
- What?
This chicken tastes like it was...
Born to be in this sauce!
My husband's saying
every time he cooked chicken.
Oh!
Well. Eric has some big news.
Go on. Tell them.
Come on. tell them!
We just hired a new underwriter.
which means I'm now an SVP
and the manager of a team of six.
That's wonderful.
The management thing
really is the best part of my job.
helping my reports
with their career development.
You know. there's a couple
of our claims reps
who are gonna be promoted
in the next quarter.
so we're gonna have some openings.
You know I don't want
to work at your insurance company.
- I have a job.
- Doing what. exactly?
Acting.
My job is to train and audition.
I just had a big one the other day.
I hear I'm probably gonna get a callback.
It's for a lead role in a Von Kovak movie.
Simon! Really?
Remind me what a "callback" is.
It's when they bring you back in
to audition again.
Any big role.
they're gonna wanna see you a few times.
Sometimes. you may even meet the director.
So it's a second interview
for a job you still might not get.
It's quite a bit more than that.
In fact. for a job of this scale.
a callback alone is a huge accomplishment.
Oh!
What exactly
are you doing at this party. man?
Sorry?
This is my mom's house.
filled with her family and friends.
How long have you known my brother?
Let's not forget that Simon
just did the American Horror Story movie!
- Mummi...
- Simon. tell your brother
about the American Horror Story.
What? What is it?
Simon. I've got to go to the loo.
I think those curried fish bites
don't exactly agree with me.
Hmm.
I want to set your expectations.
I haven't been able to find much.
Sounds like
you're not pushing hard enough.
I'm pushing.
Everyone finds it odd that I'm here.
I nearly got into a fight
with a neighbor woman.
Yeah. well. let's hope
something comes up for your sake.
- And if it doesn't?
- Then I'll find a different way
to get what I want.
- And I go back to prison?
- Yeah. So maybe keep trying.
Maybe talk to everyone. No stone unturned.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh. just getting the. um...
lab results from my doctor.
Oh.
Fabulous. Now I know I can indulge
without worrying about my cholesterol.
Hey. Hey. get you something to eat. man.
You can't be drinking all day.
Hey. look. look. I'm gonna keep it simple.
I'm drinking lemonade.
I'm not gonna get mixed up with you guys.
You know. and my mother's here!
Do you mind if I hide out in here?
Oh.
Sorry about my son. Eric can be a lot.
You shouldn't be doing dishes
at your own party.
I like to clean as I go.
It's been a lovely evening.
- And the community's charming.
- Mmm.
Sanford and I always loved it.
- A good place to raise kids.
- Hmm.
I'm glad you're here. Trevor.
You know. Simon never brought a friend
to meet the family like this.
Truthfully. he never really had a friend.
Who doesn't ever make a friend?
He's an artiste. A little prickly.
Can I tell you something?
When Simon was little.
- he fell off his bike.
- Oh!
He always insisted
on riding his father's bike.
even though he was too small for it.
It was a few years after Sanford passed.
I took him through to the kitchen.
I cleaned him up.
- And he demanded I kiss his knee.
- To kiss it better?
Exactly.
- Demanding little chap.
- Still is.
After I kissed it.
as I was putting on the Band-Aid.
he looked up and said something
he has never said again.
"Thank you for loving me. Mummi."
I thought I'd fall apart right there.
I don't know if he meant it
the way I took it
or if he was just saying something.
But all that time.
I thought he didn't mind how alone he was.
I thought. "Okay. he has his acting.
"his Criterion DVD collection.
"all those movie posters on the wall.
Maybe he doesn't feel alone."
But he was.
And he felt it. even if he didn't say it.
Anyway...
I'm glad he's got a friend.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday. dear Martha ♪
Okay! Yay!
Mummi. we gotta get going. but. uh...
Whoo!
An ice cream maker.
You were listening when I said
I wanted to be an ice cream mixologist.
- Hmm. 'Course I was.
- Mmm.
See!
Look! And it has an ingredient spout
for adding cookie bits and brownie chunks.
Uh-huh. And that looks expensive.
Which means you should probably
- be thanking me.
- Eric...
No. really. Since I'm the one who's
been supporting you.
and I paid for this kitchen.
And I know you're still giving money
to Simon. 'cause how else
would he be surviving. right?
What happened on
American Horror Story. Simon?
- Nothing.
- Bullshit!
You can't lie to me.
I'm your brother.
I got fired. okay?
- Oh. no. Simon. Really?
- No. Mummi. it wasn't my fault.
It was creative differences.
Of course.
nothing is ever your fault.
When are we gonna start bein' honest
about this problem. hmm?
Simon has no interest
in helping this family.
All he thinks about is himself.
He spends his entire life goofing off
and somehow getting encouragement
by you to keep doing it.
"Goofin' off"?
Who says "goofin' off"? Come on. man!
- No.
- I don't know what else you would call
dicking around auditioning for
over a decade with no discernible
- change in your career.
- Don't upset him!
Right. Don't upset him.
- Let's all just protect Simon's feelings.
- Atansyon. Eric.
Guy spends his own mother's money
on her birthday gift
like he's five years old.
and I'm the crazy one
for treating my grown-ass
brother like an...
What the hell. Simon?
What the hell is wrong with you?
No one's ever seen that side of me before.
Outside my family.
We don't have to talk about it.
I don't know where it all came from.
Or how it happened. I don't know why.
I wish it would all just go away.
You don't owe me an explanation.
I don't have one.
You know. I'd never work again
if anyone found out.
Why? Wha... What are you talking about?
Because of DeMarr "Doorman" Davis.
Sorry. Who's DeMarr "Doorman" Davis?
Uh...
It doesn't matter. It's not like
I have a career to worry about. anyway.
Maybe it's time for me
to admit Eric was right.
"Abide with me.
"fast falls the eventide."
What's that?
It's a hymn.
It's got me through some... tough times.
I sang it to me mum as she passed away.
That's nice. Trev. I appreciate it.
But I don't need comforting.
I need a break.
All I see is this parade
of talentless fools getting job after job.
Their dumb faces on Deadline every day.
Maybe it's time for me to admit...
That it's never gonna be me.
You don't know that.
I'm no Wonder Man.
Yeah. we should go.
Give me a sec. I need to pee.
Thanks for waiting.
Simon.
Is someone hurt? Is it your mum?
That was Janelle. my agent.
Oh. no.
Bad news? Simon. I'm... I'm so sorry.
She was trying
to get ahold of the both of us.
No one had your info.
Why?
Wha... What happened?
We both got callbacks for Wonder Man.
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
♪ Never let it fade away ♪
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
♪ Save it for a rainy day ♪
♪ For love may come
and tap you on the shoulder ♪
♪ Some starless night ♪
♪ Just in case you feel
you want to hold her ♪
♪ You'll have a pocketful of starlight ♪
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
- ♪ Never let it fade away ♪
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
- ♪ Save it for a rainy day ♪
♪ For love may come
and tap you on the shoulder ♪
♪ Some starless night ♪
♪ And just in case you feel
you want to hold her ♪
♪ You'll have a pocketful of starlight ♪
♪ Pocketful of starlight
Hm. hm. hm. hm. hm. hm ♪
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
- ♪ Never let it fade away ♪
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
- ♪ Save it for a rainy day ♪
♪ Save it for a rainy. rainy. rainy. day ♪
♪ For when your troubles
start multiplying ♪
♪ And they just might ♪
♪ It's easy to forget them
without trying ♪
♪ With just a pocketful of starlight ♪
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
- ♪ Never let it fade away ♪
♪ Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket ♪
♪ Save it for a rainy day ♪